Witness the manhunt that changed the course of human history
Risen is a action, adventure, drama film directed by Kevin Reynolds.
Clavius, a powerful Roman military tribune, and his aide, Lucius, are tasked with solving the mystery of what happened to Jesus in the
weeks following the crucifixion, in order to disprove the rumors of a risen Messiah and prevent an uprising in Jerusalem.
Clavius, played by Joseph Fiennes.
Pontius Pilate, played by Peter Firth.
Yeshua, played by Cliff Curtis.
Lucius, played by Tom Felton.
Antonius, played by Mark Killeen.
Mary Magdalene, played by María Botto.
Risen is a 2016 biblical drama film directed by Kevin
Reynolds and written by Reynolds and Paul Aiello.
An  American-Spanish co-production, the film stars Joseph Fiennes, Tom Felton, Peter Firth, and Cliff
Curtis, and details a Roman soldier's search for Jesus's body following his resurrection.
Columbia Pictures released the film to theaters in the
United States on  February 19, 2016.
It received mixed reviews and grossed $46 million worldwide.
The film explores themes of based on novel or book,
faith, christianity, crucifixion, jerusalem.
The tone is emotional and mind_bending.